<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, AlexSensation!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Alex Sensation</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    
    
    <string name="activity_animation">App/Activity/Animation</string>
    <string name="activity_animation_msg">Press a button to launch an activity with a custom animation.</string>
    <string name="activity_animation_fade">Fade in</string>
    <string name="activity_animation_zoom">Zoom in</string>
    
    
    <string name="bio">   
    
    \n\n Music is definitely one of Latinos’ biggest passions. We live it, dance it and enjoy it to the fullest. The same goes for New York City’s top Latin DJ, Alex Sensation, who works for the Hispanic radio station with the highest ratings, La Mega 97.9 FM. \n\n
Born in Bogotá, Colombia, Alex Sensation (as he is artistically known) immigrated to the United States at a young age. Influenced by his brother who was also a DJ, Alex began collecting music and at age 16 was already a disc jockey at various nightclubs. At 17 years old, he was working at the world renowned Copacabana Nightclub. In order to work at the club, he had to tell the club’s management he was 19 years old. Alex was determined to succeed and his passion for music went far and beyond. \n\n

While working at Copa, Alex was approached by Tony Luna, programming director for Amor 93.1 FM. Luna, who back then was programmer for Caliente 105.9 FM, heard Alex spinning and offered him a position as a DJ on the weekends, but only as a mixer. Alex took the job and remained with that station for about a year and a half until it switched names to Latino Mix. Six months after that switch, he was offered a job as the main mixer of a segment called “La Mega Mezcla del Mediodía” for La Mega 97.9 FM. Six years later, Alex remains the station’s most popular and successful DJ. \n\n

Besides his great mixing skills and talent, what makes Alex Sensation stand out in the radio industry? He’s multicultural, he’s charisma and he’s energy!! Alex appeals to a broad audience that includes various nationalities. He enjoys mixing different genres, but his roots as a mixer are linked with Tropical music. “I grew up listening to Salsa and Cumbia because of my roots. One of the first clubs I DJed at on the weekends was a Dominican club. There, I learned about the Dominican culture ¬¬Bachata, Merengue, Merengue típico ¬¬when I was still very young. I made many Dominican friends and fell in love with their culture.” Nowadays, his passion is everything within the Caribbean music. “I mix it all under that genre, but also knowing what the Anglo market has to offer.” Alex Sensation is truly well versed in all markets. Alex Sensation equals diversity! \n\n
Among his many accomplishments as a prominent DJ and radio personality, Alex has been the face of Dennon DJ Equipment. Alex, also DJ’s five nights a week throughout New York, New Jersey, Connecticut, Massachusetts and Long Island, just to name a few. In addition, he has two #1 mix radio shows in the #1 market in the country: “La Original Mega Mezcla and “La Mega Mezcla Sábado en la Noche” both on La Mega 97.9 FM. He also has DJed to sold¬out crowds at the Madison Square Garden, Izod Center, Nokia Theater, and the United Palace, among others. \n\n

Alex’s life revolves around music but his work does not end when he’s not in front of the microphone. He also enjoys spending time with his family and his loyal listeners. Alex is a person who has stayed true to who he is and has made sure to give back to the community. Not only is he heavily involved with the community and various charities, he also participates every year in the Puerto Rican and Dominican Parades, Colombian festivals where he has been named “Padrino Local” (Local Godfather) and the “Paz para Colombia” walk/rally in New York City. Alex is a true advocate to help the needy, children, education, and recently participated in a special fundraiser for the National Latino Commission on Aids with the President, Dennis de Leon and helped raise a substantial amount of monies for this charity. \n\n

This year, Alex received an ACE Award (the Association of Latin Entertainment Critics). He has also taken his mixes and talent to countries such as Puerto Rico, Dominican Republic, Columbia, Canada, Spain, Italy, Argentina, Ecuador, Mexico, Uruguay and Aruba. \n\n

You can listen to Alex Sensation Monday thru Friday 11AM – 3PM and Saturdays 8PM – 12 AM. Alex is also a member of the DJ Kings crew. \n\n


    
    
    </string>  
    
</resources>
